Everytime We Touch
I still hear your voice when you sleep next to me
I still feel your touch in my dreams
Forgive me my weakness but
I don't know why
Without you it's hard to survive 'Cos everytime we touch
I get this feeling
And everytime we kiss
I swear
I could fly
Can't you feel my heart beat fast?
I want this to last need you by my side 'Cos everytime we touch
I feel the static
And everytime we kiss
I reach for the sky
Can't you hear my heart beat so?
I can't let you go want you in my life
Your arms are my castle your heart is my sky
They wipe away tears that
I cry
The good and the bad times we've been through them all
You make me rise when
I fall 'Cos everytime we touch
I get this feeling
And everytime we kiss
I swear
I could fly
Can't you feel my heart beat fast?
I want this to last need you by my side 'Cos everytime we touch
I feel the static
And everytime we kiss
I reach for the sky
Can't you hear my heart beat so?
I can't let you go want you in my life 'Cos everytime we touch
I get this feeling
And everytime we kiss
I swear
I could fly
Can't you feel my heart beat fast?
I want this to last need you by my side